TSVETAN TSVETANOV

CLOUD SUPPORT ENGINEER, TECHNICAL LEAD



tsvetantsvetanov89@gmail.com Phone: (359) - 888-593756

Profile

Professional with 5+ years of experience with international businesses within complex and multicultural environments. Passionate and self-driven individual with excellent communication and problem-solving skills. I work efficiently under pressure and have strong attention to detail in order to complete strategic goals. Flexible and able to adapt to any change.

Skills Azure

Azure Serv

Automation & Windo

Configuration Management Linux

Monitoring & Alerting Docker

Server Administration Programming

Windows C#
Linux HTML
Docker PHP
Ruby

Tools

Terraform Powershell Ansible

Jenkins Bash Chef

Postman Azure CLI Puppet

Experience

Tek Experts

Active Directory IaC with ARM/Bicep

August 2020 - Present

Technical Lead - September 2021 - Present

As a Technical Lead my main responsibilities include providing technical and procedural guidance to Support Engineers directly, in daily Triages, or via Swarming Channels; performing daily quality and technical reviews on cases and leading the technical onboarding of new joiners.

L3 Engineer - February 2021 - September 2021

As a Senior Engineer in the team, besides working with customers, I was responsible for Queue Management and was tasked with helping in the onboardment of new joiners by providing mentorship after the technical training.

L2 Engineer - August 2020 - February 2021

As a Support Engineer, my main responsibilities were to provide technical assistance to customers, while resolving different problems related to the monitoring, and deployment of montioring solutions in their environments

Telus International

April 2019 - August 2020

Senior Support Representative - Decembeer 2019 - August 2020

As a Senior Support Representative, I was part of a team responsible for handling tier 1 techical escalations related to issues with an online game

Support Representative - April 2019 - December 2019

As a Support Rep for Telus, my main responsibilities were to provide basic customer support services to the users of the client services.

Education

South-West University - Blagoevgrad
Business Administration

PMG Akad. S. P. Koroliov - Blagoevgrad Mathematics/English

Certifications

Azure Administrator Associate

2023-03-04, Microsoft
AZURE
DMINISTRATOR

Containerisation CI/CD & Monitoring

2023-06-14, Software University

Containerisation CI/CD & Monitoring

2022-10-24, Software University

2023-03-28, Software University

Linux Server Administration

Windows Server Administration

C# Advanced

2022-07-25, Software University

2019-11-07, Software University

2019-06-12, Software University

Proggraming Basics with C#

Proggraming Fundamentals with C#

ONE 2019-03-12, Software University

Languages

Bulgarian
Native
English
Fluent
Italian
Basic